(Stuart:)Plus, you're forgetting
that the Infinite Crisis story line...
(Stuart:)...restored Joe Chill
to the Batman mythology.
(Sheldon:)I am forgetting nothing,
and I resent your tone.
[SIGHS]
(Stuart:)Okay. Look, Sheldon, it's late.
I've gotta get some sleep.
- So I win.
- No, I'm tired.
(Sheldon:)So I win.
- Fine, you win.
- Darn tooting, I win.
(Stuart:)Penny, I really had a terrific time.
(Stuart:)Penny?
(Sheldon:)No, no, no. Don't wake her.
(Sheldon:)She'll maul you like a rabid wolverine.
(Stuart:)You know, I don't think that was decaf.
HOWARD:
Wait, is this your card or isn't it?
(Howard:)Trust me, this was their card.
(Leonard:)I thought you were good at this.
(Leonard:)You're always talking about
how you go to bars and meet women.
(Howard:)I do. All the time.
(Leonard:)Well, what happened?
Been sitting here all night...